[Music]
thank you for calling pickin hype I'm
calling on behalf of one of my clients
I must know that what we discussed will
not go any further okay I am interested
in is it called a penis facial it's not
there's really called that it follows
all ETS but there is a penis in it
correct them so is the official term
there's no actual penis so it's not like
he's gonna get slapped in the face or
anything right exactly exactly
no right but what they do they put like
a penis in a blender and then they'll
put it on the face correct I don't think
that's exactly how it's a little bit
more scientific than that so my client
is between us Kanye West and he's
looking for a special gift for Kim okay
what he would like to do is make her her
own special penis facial using his penis
his foreskin specifically okay would it
be possible I know you said yes it would
be possible I think possible that's why
we're calling because Kanye is a
visionary as you know and yeah and then
he said you know what Terrence I've got
a little bit of extra of skin on my he
is the D word on my D word and I want to
share that with Kim's face and I want to
put that all over her okay we don't
break it down here we get it from Korea
Kanye loves Korean barbecue so I think
he's gonna like that Kanye refuses to go
to South Korea and in fact that's why he
named his daughter North is because he
loves North Korea and he admires their
leader yes oh wow so we're gonna have to
go over to North Korea to do this I love
going right to the top I do have a
couple
more questions because I can see him
right now out the window in the yard and
he's pushing on a statue and I don't
know what's Ono oh don't oh he knocked
it over okay
anyway would there be enough to share
with the whole family all the
Kardashians the Jenner's Brody Disick
everyone we want to bunnies peanuts on
everyone's face no okay so there just be
enough for Kim yeah yes okay Wow
so we've got to get your information for
these North Korean penis choppers and
then we can get Kanye's a foreskin into
the blend blend or whatever they put it
in Vitamix I don't know how it works
he's bad we don't want to do the whole
thing because he's actually saving some
of it for a shoe that he's designing
hello hello
[Music]